S
D
R
F
由第三楼字幕org调整时间轴
翻译、校对、时间轴、后期特效：狸猫
压制：wildcloudy@FRDS
在熟悉的地方，你从不会仔细观察
There are places in my neighborhood,no one ever thinks about.
你每天都会看到，但转瞬即忘
You see them every day and every day you forget about them.
这里时常会发生一些事情
These are the places where all the things happen
一些人们从不会注意的事
that people are not allowed to see.
正如你所见，布鲁克林，每晚数不清的金钱汇聚这里
You see, in Brooklyn, money changes hands all night long.
只是钱在这里可不是你存银行那么简单
It's just not the kind you can deposit in a bank.
这是所有黑钱重生的地方
All that money needs to end up somewhere.
他们称之为藏匿“包裹”
They call it a drop bar.
大老板每天晚上随机选择酒吧...
A bar the bosses choose randomly each night...
....确保藏匿的地方绝对安全
...to be the safe for an entire city.
在你的酒吧成为“藏匿之地”前你永远不会察觉
You never know up front when your bar becomes the drop bar.
你只要送走这城市城市的最脏的钱...
You just take all the city's dirtiest money...
...和所有的送包人就好...
...and bag men come and go from all over town...
...他们就如幽灵一般，来去无踪
...and nobody ever sees it coming.Nobody ever sees it going.
你所知道的仅仅是“包裹”也许下周会来
And then they could tell you to be the drop bar next week.
亦或是明年
Or maybe even next year.
问题的关键是，你从未知道
The point is, you never know.
同时...
In the meantime...
...我...
...me...
...我只是酒吧老板
...I just tend bar.
一个等待“包裹”的人
And wait.
【危险藏匿】
鲍比，你要请一轮么？
Bobby, you want to sprinkle the infield with the general?
简直爽翻了，我们已经花掉8百万美元...
This is fucking awesome. We spend $80 million...
...托这帮新泽西佬的霉运，钱都没了
...to drag a bunch of Jersey geriatrics across the river to wet-shit their depends.
够保守的
The old guard.
他们可没有
They're not that old.
你看沃克斯塔克豪斯挡拆封堵勒布朗？
You see Stackhouse block lebron with his Walker?
先生们，免费威士忌
Gentlemen, these are on the house.
当他说话时，总会有好事发生
When he speaks, he says nice things.
伙计，你可以清理一下？
Rardy, can you clean that up?
好吧，当为了里奇
Okay, if it's for Richie.
你买新裤子了，苏利？
You got new pants, Sully?
是的，我会把他们送到干洗店
Yeah, I'll send them to the dry cleaners.
-  Rardy，这可不是求你  - 去你妈的
-Rardy, we're not thanking you. -Fuck you.
那家伙他妈的可是个大块头
Fucking sphinx, that guy.
- 马文，多谢款待  - 谢谢，马文
-Cousin Marv, thanks for the drink. -Thanks, Marv.
我们能说一说孩子的事么？
Shall we say something for the kid?
- 萨利，你先来  - 是啊，萨利，别犹豫
-Sully, go ahead. -Yeah, Sully, do it up.
致敬里奇，为92年那段难忘时光
Richie "glory days" whelan. Fort Hamilton, class of '92 and a funny prick.
愿他安息
May he rest in peace.
"光辉岁月"
Glory days.
去他妈的
Fucking a.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你请他们喝了一轮
You bought them the round.
是啊 他们只是...
Yeah. They're only...
他们正在缅怀一位非常亲密的朋友，马文
They're celebrating the anniversary of a very close friend, Marv.
现在那孩子已经死了，有... 10年？
The kid's been dead, what...10 years now?
你可够傻的，为了个死人请他们喝免费威士忌
Ought to be a point where you move on. Stop scoring free drinks off a corpse.
这么说，也不应该让凳子上的美女喝免费酒？
Speaking of which, stop letting her ride a stool all night and not pay for her drinks.
- 谁，米莉？ - 是的，米莉
-Who, Millie? -Yeah, Millie.
她没有喝那么多
She doesn't drink that much.
你上次看她付账是什么时候？
When's the last time you charged her?
这是米莉，你知道的
It's Millie, you know.
因为是米莉，所以她还可以半夜在禁烟区吸烟？
After midnight, you let her smoke in here even though it's illegal.
你以为我不知道吗？
You think I didn't know that?
如果她还不付帐，今天晚上就得滚蛋
If she can't pay her tab tonight, she don't come back in here till she does.
她应该付..120刀
Her bar tab is, like, 120 bucks.
一共是140刀
It's about $140.
但她付不起，你知道的
But she can't afford it, you know?
行了，我都感动的要哭了
Yeah, I'm gonna start crying now. Okay?
把那些愚蠢的圣诞糖果清理掉，行么？
And get all the candy canes and Christmas shit down.
已经12月27日了
It's December 27th. Come on.
先生们.
Gentlemen.
我们他妈的就是群混蛋
Why don't you go fuck yourselves?
...以神之名
...hallowed be thy name.
愿君主降临，诰明圣谕，永世流传
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.
让我们每日温饱
Give us this day our daily bread.
原谅欺骗我们的人 背叛我们的人
Forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who trespass against us.
让我们远离诱惑，在罪恶中救赎自己
Lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil.
耶稣与你同在
Peace be with you.
愿主保佑
Body of Christ.
The body of Christ.
愿主保佑
这可不太好
That's not good.
你这是在做什么呢？
What are you doing in there?
行了，都好了
All right. All right, now.
嘿，在我垃圾桶这儿做什么？
Hey. What are you doing in my trash?
垃圾桶里有一只狗
You have a dog in your trash can.
被困住了
It's a boxer.
我的天
Jesus.
你垃圾里有一只狗
You have a dog here in your trash.
它正在出血
This one's bleeding.
- 你叫什么名字？鲍勃 -  吉诺
-What's your name? -Bob saginowski.
让我看看你的证件
Let me see your license.
我的证件？我的钱包在我的口袋里，你可以自己拿出来
My license? My wallet is in my pocket. You'll have to take it out.
我刚刚把图片发给4个人，知道了？
I just sent that picture to four people.We clear?
- 它冻坏了 - 是啊，它很冷
-He's freezing. -Yeah, well, it's cold.
带它进屋吧
Let's bring him inside.
顺便说下，我叫纳迪亚
I'm Nadia, by the way.
这狗还有救？
Is it bad?
我不是专家，但是，你看
It's not that deep, but, man.
这狗让人虐待惨了，看到这肿块没？
Someone beat the shit out of this dog. See these knots?
这不是脑浆，只是淤血
That's not skull, that's contusions.
你是兽医？
Are you a vet?
不，我是餐厅服务员
No, I'm a waitress at the ashmont grill.
但我整个夏天都在动物救助站做技师
But I worked at animal rescue one summer as a tech.
小心点
Careful.
太可怜了，它只是为了给小狗找个窝
They're so hard, this breed.To find them a home.
这是拳师狗？
Boxers?
这不是拳师狗，这是一种斗牛犬
This isn't a boxer. It's a pit bull.
这是一只极其危险的狗
That's a dangerous dog.
错不在狗，它的主人才是混蛋
It's not the dog's fault his owner is a dick.
这家伙...
This guy...
...看看它
...look at him.
它只是个小可爱
He's nothing but sweet.
你需要一个箱子来安置它们，我去拿一个
You'll need a crate--makes them feel safe.I have one you can borrow.
还有狗粮和嚼棒
And food and chew toys and stuff.
但是..我只是碰巧发现了，我不能..
But I was, I was just passing a garbage can. I can't--
- 我还是把它送回去  - 送给谁？虐待它的家伙？
-I'll just take him back. -To who? The guy who beat him?
那我就把它送到救助站
I'll take him to the proper authorities.
那儿将是它的家
That would be the shelter.
好吧
Right.
之后，他们给主人七天时间
After they give the owner seven days
如果他还决定抛弃这只狗...
to reclaim him, if he decides not to...
...这狗就会被拿出来领养
...this dog will be put up for adoption.
但是谁会领养这只狗？
But who knows what kind of person will take him?
我不知道
I don't know.
你可以的，给它一个家
You can take him. You take him.
我晚上工作，有很多活要干
I work nights. I work a lot.
给我我只能把它送到救助站
We'll have to send him to animal rescue.
好吧，这样，你看你能..你能不能...
Okay, look, can you, can you...
...给我一两天去考虑？-求你了
...give me a couple days to think about it? Please?
我需要好好考虑下，这不是个轻松的活
I have to think about this. It's a big responsibility.
对于养狗我一窍不...
I don't know anything about--
没关系，就几天，我会回来
please, just a couple days. I'll come back.
求你，抱着它，周末我就过来
Please, a couple days. Hold him till the weekend.
到周末，就几天，求你了...
Just the weekend. It's a couple days. Please. Please.
周六上午
Saturday morning.
谢谢
Thank you.
就这样，谢谢
All right. Thank you.
星期六
Saturday.
鲍勃？
Bob?
- 这狗需要一个名字 - 没错。
-The dog needs a name. -Right.
噢 我的天啊...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
你会好起来的
You're going to be okay.
你知道一个纳迪亚邓恩的人么？纳迪亚邓恩？
Do you know a Nadia Dunn? Nadia Dunn?
你知道么？
You don't?
你不知道？
不
No.
就是牵着这只狗的女孩
That's the girl who's holding the dog.
又是狗
The dog again.
你知道，我在想，怎么训练这只狗...
You know, I was thinking that training a dog...
...看家，而且所有这一切，这是...
...housebreaking, and all that, that's...
...我的意思是，这是一个大责任，对不对？
...I mean, that is a huge responsibility, right?
嗯，这只是一只狗
Well, it's a dog.
它可不像一些坐在轮椅里腰上挂着尿袋的..
It's not like some long-lost retarded relative shows up in a wheelchair...
...老年痴呆症患者
...a colostomy bag hanging out of his ass.
说，“我是你的了，照顾好我”
Says, "I'm yours now. Take care of me."
而它不是
It's not that.
只是一只狗
It's a dog.
是啊
Yeah.
什么？
What?
不
No.
这主意糟透了
It's a fucking bad idea.
这一切太好笑了，就当这事没发生过好么
We should hit it for everything or not at all.
哥们，听着。我的良心告诉我，我们得给它...
Little brother, listen. My guy says we got to show him...
...给他找一个归宿
...that we can handle our shit.
我们这样做，看看狗的主人是何反应
Says we do it in steps. See how the owners respond.
他们会以为你是个山炮，你个傻逼
They could respond pretty fucking bad, you nut.
所以我们应该尝试下
So that's what we'll see.
你这个家伙，说这么一大堆废话
Your guy. Your fucking guy talks a whole hell of a lot.
这是一个他妈的“包裹"
It's a fucking drop bar.
今晚可没有
Not tonight it isn't.
就这样？
Okay?
好吧
Okay.
别管别的，给它装满
Don't think about it, just fill it.
好吧，别给我们惹麻烦
Okay, we won't cause any trouble.
这里麻烦的只有你
You're making trouble!
- 你知道你在他妈的做啥呢？ - 马文
-Do you know what the fuck you're doing? -Marv.
你知道这是谁的钱吗？
Do you know whose money this is?
让你装就赶紧的
Fucking fill the bag!
好吧
All right.
放松点
Just take it easy.
就这样
There you go.
这样可以了吗
Go ahead.
你他妈说得太多了
You fucking talk too much.
rardy在哪儿？
Where's rardy?
Rardy？
Rardy?
哎我草..
What the fuck?
- 你没事吧？ - 哦，老天，吓尿了
-You all right? -Oh, God, I'm gonna be sick.
- 我没事 - 看他的头
-I'm okay. -Look at his head.
他让人削了 快叫救护车
Split open. We got to call an ambulance.
这真糟糕， Rardy，呆在这里，不要动
That's bad. Rardy, don't move.Just stay where you are.
- 我看起来多糟糕？ - 不要动，除非你想变植物人
-How bad do I look? -Don't move. It's not good.
我在你脑袋上放条毛巾
I'm putting something on your head.
按住
Hold that.
还有你脸上
There's one for your face.
St.dom's 早8点
The 8 o'clock at St. dom's.
每天早上，我们匆匆遇见，又擦肩而过
Every morning we see each other and we've never met.
-探员万德罗托雷斯  - 嗨，我是鲍勃
-Detective evandro Torres. -Hi. I'm Bob saginowski.
- 关于St. dom's我很抱歉 - 你是什么意思？
-A shame about St. dom's. -What do you mean?
我只是发现了他们改名为圣玛利亚，你能相信吗？
I just found out they're folding it into St. Mary's. Can you believe that?
我不知道你说什么
I did not know that.
- 你是这儿的调酒师？ - 是啊
-You're the bartender? -Yeah.
谈谈这抢劫案吧  -出来聊聊？
The guys with the guns--  want to take a walk?
你认为他们中有没有人曾经来过你这里？
They sound like anyone who ever came in here before?
应该有，离我最近的家伙，它手表坏了，我记得
Nah. The guy closest to me,I could see that his watch had stopped.
官员贝尔纳多说，你报告他们从头到尾没露面？
Officer Bernardo says you said they were covered head to toe? Hoodies, masks?
是的，但我可以看到他的手腕，他转过来的时候
Yeah, but I could see his wrist as it was turning.
手表就这样露在我面前，像这样
The face of the watch was in front of me, like that.
- 手表停了？ - 是的，停在6:15
-And it was stopped? -Yeah. It said 6:15.
他从你这里抢走多少？
How much they take you for?
收银机里所有的钱
Well, whatever was in the register.
那么，我不会听说你这里有赌博...
So, if I was to ask around,I wouldn't hear anything about...
...或者关于洗钱什么的事情，对吧？
...anyone making book here, or someone moving money around?
你这是什么意思？
Excuse me?
- 你没干那些事情？ - 没有
-I wouldn't hear that? -Nah.
- 你有保险吗，rardy？ - 你认为呢？
-Do you have insurance, rardy? -What do you think?
不，我们没有保险
No, we don't have insurance.
- 整个事情真是一团糟  - 是的，他被人白揍一顿
-The whole thing's a travesty.-Yeah, he took a pretty bad hit.
不，是说关于St. dom's的事
Nah, I meant St. dom's.
好 好！
Yeah. Yeah.
美丽的教堂，他们做的真好
Beautiful church. They did mass right.
没有唱诗班 祈祷结束后也没有拥抱
No group hugs after the our father.No folk singers.
当他们玩闹够了 这教堂...
By the time the seculars get done persecuting the church...
...留下来的不过一扇扇窗户，还有上边的彩色玻璃
...all we'll have left is a bunch of condos with stained glass windows.
那边的监控探头出什么毛病了？
What's up with the surveillance cameras in there?
那只是个空壳，只是为了吓唬罪犯
They don't record. They're just a deterrent for crime.
你怎么从不领圣餐？
Why don't you take communion?
什么？
Excuse me?
这么多年我在弥撒看到你很多次，你从没领过圣餐
I've seen you at mass for years. You haven't taken communion once.
这个，你知道的，个人隐私
Well, you know, that's my business.
你说呢？是吧？
You think so, huh?
是啊，我也这么认为
Yeah, I think so.
老天，我他妈的就知道这样
Jesus. I fucking know so.
所以他还是不相信你...
So was he gonna let you wear his letter jacket...
......还是他还在试探你？
...or did he have to twist your nipples a few times first?
你他妈的和警察说那块表干啥？
Why the fuck would you tell that cop about the watch?
- 我不知道 - 你不知道
-I don't know. -You don't know.
就是这样说出去了
It just came out.
那好 以后在说话的时候 走点脑子！
Well, next time, why don't you nip that impulse in the bud?
你他妈的这是怎么了？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
这一点不像我，马文
It was very unlike me, Marv.
他们拿走我们5千多元
They took us for five thou and some change.
五千？
Five thousand?
还好他们只拿走信封那些，所以还没那么糟糕
Thank God they picked up the envelope, so we're not on the hook for that.
这和我们没多少关系
So we're all right. We're okay.
不，他们拿走了我们五千美元还有一些零钱
No, they took us for five large and some change.
这些是“包裹”里的东西，他们的钱
It's their bar, it's their money.
他们会来要账的，所以离他妈的没事还远着呢
They're going to want it back.So we're not so fucking okay.
鲍勃？
Bob?
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
-You all right? -Yeah.
- 谁知道明天会发生什么 - 是啊，我想我们只能等了
-Kind of early for the eight. -Yeah. I figured I could wait.
好吧，进来吧
Well, come on in.
这只是一些狗粮
It's just a bowl and some food.
谢谢，谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
- 祝好运  - 谢谢
-Good luck. -Thank you.
你知道，我以前从来没有养过狗...
You know, I've never owned a dog before...
...所以，你知道...
...so, you know...
我不知道该怎么做
I have no idea what I'm doing. At all.
你需要这个
You'll need bowls.
一条狗链
A leash.
狗便袋
Poop bags.
从现在开始，鞋要放到架子上
And from now on, keep your shoes up on a shelf.
让我看看，如果我能找到放在床上那个..
Let me see if I can find the bed section.
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
这是我知道的最好的书了，你应该看看
This is the best book I know. You should read it.
一切都在这里
Everything is in here.
给它想好名字了吗？
What are you naming him?
好吧，我想叫它洛克，我喜欢洛克这个名字
Well, I was thinking about maybe rocco. I like the name rocco.
好像迈克也不错
But then I thought Mike.
迈克？
Mike?
- 你不喜欢迈克？ - 迈克可不是一个好名字
-You don't like Mike?  -No. Mike is not a great name for a dog.
洛克好一些
Rocco is better.
那就洛克
Okay.
所以你是因为做体操运动员后才叫纳迪亚么？
So did they name you Nadia after the gymnast?
- 是啊  - 所以，你是一个体操运动员？
-Yeah. -So you're a gymnast?
不
No.
干得好，看到了吗？
Here you go. See?
“洛克”。嘿，它喜欢这个名字
"Rocco". Hey, he likes it.
是啊，我还是喜欢迈克
Yeah, I like Mike.
- 你领养它了？ - 是啊
-You have him? -Yeah.
养狗需要耐心
Be patient.
再见，谢谢你
Bye, thank you.
“别忘了给盒子两边加上垫子”
"Make sure the bottoms of the two side panels rest inside the bottom."
嘿，洛克？
Hey, rocco?
我给你找个安全的窝
I made you a safe place.
鲍勃？
Bob?
冷了吧？
Cold one, huh?
有鲍勃你这暖男谁怕冷？
Who needs snow blower when you have Bob?
也许一会应该去我那里一趟
Maybe you come to my house later.
当然
Sure.
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
是我……囧
This guy.
你现在很安逸？
You on the welfare?
什么？
Excuse me?
鲍勃干了所有的活，看看吧
Bob does all the work. You watch.
不，我在铲
No, I was shoveling.
- 你也在铲雪，好吧  - 他在做
-You're shoveling, all right.  -He was.
过来
Come.
你认识这个人？
You know this guy?
不
No.
但我认识这家伙
But I know this guy.
当我想要知道的时候我无所不知
Moment I know him, I know him.
有人抢走我的“包裹"
Somebody robbed my bar.
额，是的，这事很抱歉，Umarov先生
Yes. That's right. I'm sorry, Mr. umarov.
Umarov先生是我老子
Call my father Mr. umarov.
鲍勃·...
Bob...
...叫我Chovka，恩？
...call me chovka, eh?
好吧，对不起，Chovka先生，的确有人抢走你的“包裹”
That's right, I'm sorry, Mr. chovka somebody did rob your bar.
谁抢了我“包裹”？
Who robbed our bar?
我不知道，他们戴着面具
We don't know. They wore masks.
他说的对，我们看不到他们的脸
That's right. So we couldn't see.
警方报告说，其中一个人带着一块坏表
Police report says one wore a broken watch.
这是你告诉他们的？
You tell them this?
是的，当时我刚出来，没考虑那么多
Yeah, I did. I wasn't thinking. It just came out.
那么你们打算怎么把我父亲的钱找回来？
So what are you doing to get my father's money back?
好吧，这么说
Well, we put the word out.
- 抢钱的人就在这附近 - 他说的没错
-In the neighborhood. -That's right.
他们说钱就在这附近
They got the word out in the neighborhood.
你的意思就是在附近，是吧？
So the word is out there, huh?
- 是这样 - 恩
-The word. -That's right.
那是我的钱
With my money.
他妈的我要知道那笔钱在哪儿
Find my fucking money.
“找回那笔钱”
"Find my money."
如果我们知道那笔钱在哪儿，我们就知道谁抢了我们
If we knew where their money was,it would mean we knew who robbed us.
这意味着我们趟进这趟浑水
Which would mean we were in on it
得和那帮抢劫犯面对面谈判
which means they'd shoot us in the face.
他妈的车臣
Fucking chechnyans.
车臣，马文
Chechens, Marv.
他们是来自车臣，但你叫他们车臣分子
They're from chechnya, but you call them chechens.
是啊，车臣
Yeah, chechnya.
我说你从不说爱尔兰的人是爱尔兰佬，不是么？
I said that. You don't call people from Ireland irelandians, do you?
你他妈的再说什么？
What the fuck are you talking about?
哟，哟，睡前点心是什么？
Yo, yo. What's the sunset nightcap this evening?
-拿你自己的杯子？ - 什么，我又没那么没见世面
-You bring your own cup? -What, I just got out of the womb?
- 干杯  - 干杯
-Cheers. -Salud.
发生什么了，伊万德罗？
So what up, evandro?
你还记得马文？
You remember Marvin stipler?
马文？
Cousin Marv?
他弄丢了九，十年前车臣分子留在这儿的一个“包裹”
He got pushed off his own book, nine, ten years ago, by the chechens.
那个“包裹”，是他老子Umarov的一个皮包公司的
His bar got held up. It's owned by one of papa umarov's shell companies.
什么样的蠢货会去抢劫“包裹”藏匿之地？
What kind of dumb-ass holds up one of his bars?
问住我了
You got me.
一来就对Umarov下手？
Major crimes up on the umarovs?
我们靠削减预算才勉强支撑下来
We barely survived the last budget cuts.
我们不想因为俄罗斯那子虚乌有的组织浪费钱财
We're not sticking our heads up to go after some Russian John q barely knows exists.
车臣
Chechen.
他是你的了
You want him, he's all yours.
嘿，你准备好吃饭了吗？
Hey, baby brother, you ready to eat?
- 什么？ - 准备好吃饭没？
-What?  -Are you ready to eat?
不
No.
我吃了
I ate already.
- 我吃过了  - 你什么时候吃的？
-I ate already. -When did you eat?
我吃过了
I ate.
哦，不  嘿，嘿，别介
Oh, no. Hey, hey, no.
洛克，呆在那里，坐下
Rocco, stay there. Stay.
不要这样做
Don't do it.
别动，不要跳
Don't do it. Don't jump.
耶了个稣的
Crikey Jesus.
就差一点
That was close.
你真是我的祖宗
You gave me a heart attack.
- 你他妈的去哪儿了 - 我刚到
-Where the fuck you been? -Getting here.
- 你拿到了钱？ - 没
-You got the money? -No.
- 不是什么意思？ - 我的意思就是他妈的没拿到
-What do you mean, no? -I mean no 'cause fucking bri has it.
你大爷
Bri has it.
- 有没有和你哥透漏我的消息？ - 没有
-Did you tell your brother about me? -No.
让你干点事怎么这么难？
Why the fuck you hit rardy so hard?
- 我得... - 你必须
-I had to.  -You had to.
当时我只能叫救护车，所以那儿有警察和医生
And I had to call an ambulance. So there's an ambulance and cops.
他的手表怎么了？
What's with his watch?
人们注意到那是块坏表，告诉他去买块新的
People noticed it's broke. Tell him to get a new one and get rid of that one.
就是今天
Today.
下一步怎么办？什么时候抢个真的“包裹”？
What's the next step? When do we hit a real drop bar?
我只是假设，我不是个没长脑袋的混蛋，知道不？
Let's just assume I'm not some asshole without a plan, okay?
假设一个航班失事，明天最安全的航线是那条？
When an airplane goes down, what's the safest airline to fly the next day?
失事的那条
The one that had the crash.
对，就是这个意思
Right. There you go.
所以我们只需要等待
So we just wait.
你说的我一个字都没听懂
I don't understand a fucking word you're saying.
就像你在说鸟语
It's like you're speaking Brazilian.
照顾好它就行，可以么？
Just let me take care of it, okay?
低点头
Keep your head down.
这不是巴西人，巴西人说葡萄牙语
It's not Brazilian. Brazilians speak Portuguese.
你要去哪儿？
Where you going?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
呆在这儿，我们不能同时露面，傻瓜
Stay here. We can't be seen together, genius.
- 他妈的，得呆多久？ - 我不知道，也许十分钟
-Fuck you. How long? -I don't know. Ten minutes!
坐
Sit.
坐  不，那是站，过来
Sit. No, that's standing. Come here.
走，走  哦，伙计
Go, go. Oh, man.
你好吗？
How you doing?
很好
Good.
Shit 洛克，加油！
Shit. Rocco, come on!
来吧  好孩子
Come. Good boy.
你没看过这本书，是吗？
You didn't read the book, did you?
看过一点..额...
Some of it, yeah. No.
不是很多
Not a lot.
我在想....现在假期结束了...
I was thinking--now the holiday's over...
...我不在那家餐馆上班了
...I lost a shift at the restaurant.
对不起
I'm sorry.
也许你可以给我提供份工作
So maybe you could hire me, you know?
帮你工作的时候照顾洛克？
Pay me to babysit rocco when you're working?
那个，也不算坏主意
Hey, well, that's not such a bad idea.
我在酒吧工作很长时间了
I work a lot at the bar.
你会很满意的
That would be very kind of you.
给我留个电话？
You have a number I can call?
也许安排好我就给你打电话
Maybe call. You want to arrange this properly?
放在那里就好
Just put it there.
- 你有笔没？ - 没
-Have you got a pen? -No.
我想我有一只
I think I have a pen.
需要的时候总是找不到
Where's that pen when you need it?
- 能写字不？ - 没问题
-Does it work?  -Yeah.
给你
Here you go.
不错，这是一个好主意
Great. That's a great idea.
我还需要一把钥匙
And I need a key.
这样就好了......如果你给我打电话，你就可以...
Well, like, maybe I could... If you call me, I'll either have it...
...交给我，或者离开前放在酒吧这里.
...and drop it around yours, or I could leave it at the bar for you.
打电话给我。
Call me.
是的，我会打电话给你...你已经给我号码了
Yeah, I'll call you...On this number you gave me right now.
顺便祝..新年快乐
Happy new year, by the way!
新年快乐！
Happy new year!
我们应该加入表演
We should join that show.
你会唱歌么？
You can't fucking sing.
不是这个，另一个，那里的人们......
Not that one, the other one, where the people...
...去世界各地寻找线索
...go around the world picking up clues and stuff.
听起来不错，来吧
It'd be cool. Let's do it.
我们可以看到一些东西
We could see things.
啥?
What things?
我不知道，其它国家
I don't know. Other countries.
其他方式
Other ways.
你今天看到老头？
You see the old man today?
是，我就是
Yeah, I was by.
他们希望拿回自己的钱，马文。
They want their money, Marv.
什么人？
Who?
这里的居民
The home.
他们会拿到的
They'll get it.
这是讨债公司，不是邻居
It's the collection agency now, not the home.
医疗补助削减，我不干了
Medicaid cutbacks. Me retiring.
他们打算把他运出去
They're going to ship him out.
到哪里？
To where?
一个偏僻的地方
To a lesser place.
也许现在是时候了
Maybe it's time.
是的
Yeah.
做掉他
Just kill him.
我们的父亲，他是个麻烦
Our father. Because it's inconvenient.
他已经死了，马文
He's dead, Marv.
那么机器里传出来的哔哔声是...
So what are all those beeps coming out of the machines...
...还有屏幕上的波浪线是什么？
...he's hooked up to, and the waves on the screen of the thing?
那就是生命
That's life.
这只是电，你以为呢
That's electricity, is what that is.
有一天，我把他的手放在我的脸上
The other day, I picked up his hand and put it on my cheek.
我听到血液在流动
And I could hear his blood.
所以你要干掉他？去做吧，你的决定
So you want to unplug him? Go ahead, your decision.
冷静！
Take it easy.
不，作出决定，我已经准备好了
No, make the decision. I'll be all right with it.
这会是第一个
That'd be a first.
没关系，没关系
Never mind. It's okay.
我会到欧洲过另一种生活
I'll get to Europe in another life.
洛克，过来
Rocco. Come to heel.
过来，过来，坐！
Come to heel. Come to heel. And sit.
- 你看到了吗？ - 是的，我看到了
-You see that? -Yeah, I saw it.
它还想握手
He almost gave me the paw.
当我看电视的时候，它在我腿上睡着了
When I watch TV, he sleeps on my leg.
- 真的吗？ - 假的
-Really?  -Out.
- 来吧  - 我马上就回来
-Come.  -I'll be right back.
哦，来吧
Crazy. Come on.
这狗真漂亮
That's a nice dog.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you. I appreciate it.
是啊，这是一个非常漂亮的狗
Yeah, that's a nice-looking dog.
不要忘记喂它
Don't forget to feed it.
告诉我这附近哪儿有医院？
Tell me where the hospital is?
掉头，然后沿着这条路走到头
Bang a u-ey, go down to the end here.
右转，你会看到路标
Take a right. There'll be signs.
谢谢
Thanks.
我答应你，明天去公园，今天我快忙死了
I promise, tomorrow we'll go to the park. But I'm in a mad rush today.
我一会就回来
I will be back very soon.
嘿，伙计，你在干嘛？
Hey, man, how you doing?
不介意我进去么？外边有点冷
Mind if I step in? It's kind of cold outside.
多谢
Thanks a lot.
我的天
Jesus.
需要帮忙么？
Can I help you?
是啊，你把它养在哪里？
Yeah. Where are you keeping him?
你在胡说些什么？
What are you talking about?
那只狗，你让它呆在厨房，地下室？
The dog. You keep him in the kitchen? The cellar?
我记得你，在公园里你跟我说我有一只漂亮的狗
I remember you. You came up to me in the park and told me I had a nice-looking dog.
是啊，只不过那不是你的狗
Yeah, well, he's not your dog.
不，那是我的狗
Yeah, he's my dog.
是吗？你有注册麽？
Yeah? You register him?
城市管理条例规定你必须为狗注册
City says you have to license it. How about a chip?
- 什么？ - 一个安全芯片
-Excuse me?  -A security chip.
植入狗身体的芯片，这样兽医扫描的时候就能识别..
Implanted in the dog. Pooch goes missing, shows up at a vet. Vet scans the dog.
这是流浪狗还是某人的宠物
Up pops a barcode with the owner's info.
狗的主人也会有一张证明
The owner, meanwhile, walks around with a slip of paper.
上边记有安全芯片的序列号
It has the security chip account number on it.
让我看看
Check it out.
这是我的狗
You got my dog.
不，这是我的狗。
No, it's my dog.
你虐待过它
You beat him.
我会告诉警察你虐待动物
I'll tell the cops you did.
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
今天真是个好天气，不是么？
It's kind of sunny, right?
不过你永远不会明白，我猜
But you never know, I guess.
你从来没问过
You never ask about it.
你是我遇见的唯一一个5分钟没有问这个问题的人
You're the only person I ever met who didn't ask about it in the first five minutes.
那是你的隐私，不是我的
It's your business, not mine.
如果你不想隐瞒，迟早你会告诉我，又何必问呢？
You'll tell me when you tell me, or you won't.
我自己弄得，这让我觉的很high
I did it to myself. I was pretty high.
你自己弄得？
You did that?
用这个...
With one of those...
......就像削皮器
...like, a peeler.
削皮器？
Peeler?
你知道，土豆削皮器
You know, a potato peeler?
哦，天啊，是的，我知道那是什么
Oh, God, yeah, I know what that is, right.
我和其他人不同，我有时候很讨厌自己
I was a different person then. I didn't really like myself.
你喜欢现在的自己？
Do you like yourself now?
先生，这里不允许携带宠物，把它领出去行不？
Sir, you cannot have a dog in here. Dog goes, you guys go, okay?
我告诉你...
I'm telling you...
-  ...有人跟踪我 - 不，没有
-...I got guys following me. -You don't.
我确信，我跟你说过车上那个家伙
I do. I told you about the guy in the car.
他向你问过路
He was asking you for directions.
这是在路上，仅仅是巧合碰到一起
It was the way he asked. The way he was looking at me.
我他妈的不是白痴
I'm not a fucking idiot.
你呢？一个拿伞的人
What about you? The guy with the umbrella.
他只是对他的狗有兴趣
He's just interested in the dog.
狗
The dog.
你怎么知道，也许只是他告诉了你
How do you know? Maybe he's just telling you that.
对他们来说要...
It's too much for them to...
...找到并且归还原处，现在实在太温和了
...put them back where they found them, because that would require courtesy.
你只需要拿个垃圾桶，马文
You should just get a dumpster, Marv.
“你只需要搬个垃圾桶，马文，拿个垃圾桶过来”
"Just get a dumpster, Marv. Get a dumpster."
当然
Sure.
你还记得我没有“包裹”了，对不对？
You remember I don't own the bar anymore, right?
是啊
Yeah.
是的，但你的“包裹”不是让Chovka拿走了
Yeah, but it's not your bar chovka took.
那是10年前的事了
That was 10 years ago.
不，这是八年半年前
No, it was eight-and-a-half years ago.
好了
All right.
八年半
Eight-and-a-half years.
多蒂认为我们应该去欧洲
Dottie thinks we should visit Europe.
像十年前和他妹妹去欧洲的哪个人
That's what I've become-a guy that goes to Europe with his sister.
上了一辆...一辆...游览车...
Hops in a, a tour bus...
...脖子上挂着相机，看上去像个蠢货
...with a fucking camera around my neck like a fucking jerkoff.
什么？
What?
你需要了解这一点，马文
You need to see this, Marv.
不，我不
No, I don't.
我不需要做任何事情
I don't need to do anything.
我就想站在这里，我他妈的哪儿都不想去
I'm just going to stand right here. I'm going to stand right the fuck here.
不
No.
你真应该看看这个
You really should take a look at this.
我不想看到欧洲，不像看到多蒂
I don't need to see Europe. I don't need to see dottie.
所以我也不像看到那个什么袋子
And I don't need to see what's in that bag.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
我们现在做点什么？
We need to do something with it.
什么，钱还是...
What, the money or the...
...事情吗？
...thing?
我打赌，这里多出来的那些东西就是那晚我们丢掉的
I bet what's in here adds up to what we lost that night.
他们为什么把这个给我们？
Why'd they give it back to us?
我们应该还给他们
So we give it back to them.
他们想要这个
That's clearly what they expect.
就像包住一块肉
Like you're wrapping a piece of meat.
向你平时一直做的那样
Like you've done it a thousand times.
难道你没看出来如果你没有提到手表...
Do you wonder if you hadn't mentioned the watch...
不，我不
No, I don't.
嗯，我知道
Well, I do.
嗨，你那儿有zima没？
Hi, guys. You got any zima?
不，我们关门了
No, we're closed.
好了，你的门没上锁，所以...
Well, your door was unlocked, so--
我很抱歉，但是我们现在正准备关闭，所以...
I'm sorry about that, but we're closed now, so...
好吧，好吧！
Yeah. Yeah.
你得走了
You got to go.
嘿，鲍勃
Hey, Bob.
你好吗？很高兴见到你
How you doing? Nice to see you.
来吧
All right, come on.
和纳迪亚打声招呼
Say hi to Nadia.
当她在身上添新伤口的时候别忘了把她缝好，没问题？
Don't forget to stitch her up when she stabs herself, okay?
我们把那只手像火腿一样扔来扔去...
Tossing the missing piece of the one-armed man around like a ham...
...结果前门还没锁！
...and the front door's open!
- 他什么也没看见  - 但他可能已经看到了
-He didn't see anything. -But he could've.
但是他并没有
But he didn't.
你知道那个人吗？
You know that guy?
是的，这就是说关于洛克事情的那个家伙
Yeah. That's the guy I told you about with rocco.
那个声称是狗主人的人？
Who claims the dog is his?
不是他还是谁？
You know who else he is?
不
No.
他是声称自己杀死富翁Whelan的人
He's the guy who says he killed Richie whelan.
- 那家伙？ - 没错
-That guy? -Yeah.
- 这是Eric deeds？ - 是啊，这是Eric deeds
-That's Eric deeds? -Yeah, that's Eric deeds.
还骗了我们的那个人
And he's fucked in the squash, that guy.
已经有好几次了
Been in the joint a couple times.
如果我没记错他在杜鹃屋住了30天
He did a 30-day in the cuckoo house, if I recall.
所以，你看这小子
So you watch that fucking kid.
这一天天的，马文
Some fucking day, Marv.
是啊，操蛋的一天
Yeah, some fucking day.
帮我把那个运动包从上边拿下来？
Will you pass me the sports bag by the wasp-and-ants spray?
没问题，当然，我很乐意
Yeah, sure, I'd love to.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在我要出去走走
I'm going for a walk now.
好
Okay.
去他妈的耶稣
Fucking Christ.
别看这儿，别看
Don't look at that. Don't look at it.
嘿，嘿，这是什么？
Hey, hey, what's this?
把它拿回来，去
Go get it. Go on.
是啊，好好玩，这红色骨头
Yeah, play with it. My big red bone.
把他拿回来，拿回来
Go get it. Go get that!
去找骨头
Get the bone!
该死
Shit.
Saginowski先生
Mr. saginowski.
- 你好吗？ - 我很好
-How you doing? -I'm good.
我们还没抓到他们
We haven't caught them yet.
是啊，你知道的，我以为...
Yeah, well, you know, I assumed...
我们没努力去找？
That we didn't do our job?
不，我只是听说，很难逮捕到抢劫犯
No, I just heard it was hard to make an arrest on robbery cases.
- 这包是怎么回事？ - 这是...
-What's up with the bag?  -This is...
这是狗狗的便袋，有时我把狗链和球...
It's my poop bag and sometimes I keep leashes and balls...
...之类的东西在我的包里。
...and stuff in my bag.
怎么是空的
Kind of empty.
是啊，我用了最后一个狗便袋，球也丢了
Yeah, well, I used my last poop bag and I lost the ball.
Richie whelan.
- 他怎么样？ - 你知道他吗？
-What about him? -You know him?
当然，前天他和朋友在这儿呆一整天
Sure. His friends were in the bar the other day
纪念他的朋友
toasting his anniversary.
什么纪念日？
What anniversary?
纪念他最后一次现身
Of the last time anybody saw him.
在我的酒吧里
Which was at your bar.
是啊，就是这样，他就走了
That's right. Yeah, he left.
他开走了车，不久他们就发现了他
He took his car and they found it someplace.
已经烧焦了
这是只漂亮的狗
That's a good-looking dog.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道 Eric deeds？
You know an Eric deeds?
高高的？络腮胡？就像一个沉思者？
Tall guy? Beard? He's, like, a brooder?
也许吧
Maybe.
你可以在酒吧工作的，老兄
I mean, you working in that bar. Come on.
你认识很多人的，对吗？
You know people, Mr. saginowski.
我有张照片
I got a picture.
恩，你也许认为是他抢了“包裹”
Nah. You think maybe he robbed the bar?
不
No.
我听到这里，还有那里，这家伙...
I'm hearing here and there that this guy...
...和Whelan消失有关
...has something to do with the whelan disappearance.
真的吗？
Really?
这真是一个非常漂亮的狗
That's a really good-looking dog.
我过来陪他下午溜溜
I came by to give him his afternoon walk.
好嘛
Great.
我很惊讶，你电话开着？
I freaked. Is your cell on?
是的，震动，我没感觉到
Yeah, but it's on vibrate. I couldn't feel it.
我打了好几个电话
I called a bunch of times.
我知道，我知道的，对不起
I know, I could see that. I'm sorry.
- 我以为你今天工作  - 我，我只是要...
-I thought you were working today. -I am, it's just I had this...
你知道吗？这说来话长了
You know what? It's a really long story.
对不起，我应该给你打电话的 我道歉
I'm sorry. I should have called you. I apologize.
没关系的
It's okay. Hey.
所以，你知道 Eric deeds，是吧？
So you know Eric deeds, huh?
不，我不是很了解这个人
No. I don't "know him" know him...
...你知道？我只听别人说过
...you know? I know him from around.
所以，你不认识他？
So you don't know him?
不确定，应该不认识
Not really, no.
这很有意思，因为从他说话方式，我想...
That's funny, because the way he said it, I figured...
想到什么？
Figured what?
我不知道，也许...
I don't know. You know, maybe...
- 我不知道  - 你为什么追问这个？
-I don't know. -Why are you on my ass about it?
我只问了一个问题..
I was just asking a question.
不，你在暗示我这个问题
No, you were insinuating.
不，我没有
No, I wasn't.
现在你只需直接和我说就行
Now you're arguing just to argue with me.
不
No.
- 看到了吗？ - 我不是
-See?  -I'm not.
我不需要这玩意，好吗？
I don't need this shit, okay?
等下，这里发生了什么？难道我说错什么了？
Wait. What happened here? Did I say something wrong?
你以为我很好欺负？
You think you can push me around?
不，等等
No. Wait.
别他妈的碰我
Don't you fucking touch me.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我问她一个问题
I asked her one question.
一个简单的问题，然后我就被轰出来了
A question. Simple. And then it all came out sideways.
你还不明白，他们现在很生气...
You don't get it. They get in a mood...
...对他们来说，希望越大失望越大
...you could give them the hope diamond and they'd complain about the weight.
我说得对不对？
Am I right?
鲍勃，你是不是在谈论一个女孩，对吧？
Bob, you ain't actually talking about a girl, are you?
波比给自己买了一个女孩？
Bobby's got himself a girl?
男人养狗，就会变成吸妹子的磁铁
Guy gets a dog, becomes a pussy magnet.
现在她们已经投怀送抱了
They're flinging it at my man now.
我去打杆台球
I'm gonna go play some pool.
你怎么了？
How are you?
Chovka，我们喝一杯
Chovka, let me get you a drink.
马文？斯特拉...安德烈，他要斯特拉。
Marv? Stella--Andre, he drinks Stella.
看啊
There you go.
在这儿
Here it is.
我把它放在一个保鲜袋里，都在这儿了，你可以点下
I put it in a ziploc. But it's all there. You can count it.
保鲜袋？
Ziploc?
嗯，这个有点湿
Well, it was a little wet.
我想要弄干它，可是我们没有烘干机
I was going to dry it, but we don't have a dryer.
所以我只能放到个保鲜袋里，如果你拿出来...
So I figured I'd put it in a ziploc. If you spread it out...
...放在桌子上凉一早上，应该就没问题了
...on a table, it should be good come the morning.
我不知道你在说什么，鲍勃
I have no idea what you're talking about, Bob.
这不是你上次给我的酒
This isn't what you gave me last time.
哦，这不是18号威士忌
That? No, that's not the bowmore 18.
你不喜欢这个，你说这闻起来像香港脚
You didn't like it. You said it smelled like feet.
我想你会更喜欢这个，很特别的
I figured that you would prefer this a lot more. This is very special.
爱尔兰人
It's Irish.
我们都会死
We die.
所有的人...
All of us...
...安德烈。
...Andre.
但是在这之前，你一定要试试这威士忌
But before you do, you have to try this fucking whiskey, man.
好啊，给他来一杯，这里
Yeah, get him one. Come on. Here.
轮到你为“包裹”坐庄了
You handle the drop.
好吧，哪天？
All right. Which night?
超级碗决赛
Super bowl.
好
Okay.
酒不错
Is good.
埃万德罗 托雷斯 探长
Detective evandro Torres.
- 吉米 沙利文 - 太感谢你了
-Jimmy Sullivan. -Thanks for seeing me.
所以他消失的那天 你不知道其他什么消息了么
So you got nothing else about the night glory days vanished?
我唯一记得的就是他离开酒吧去买大麻了
The only thing I remember was that he left the bar to score weed.
一起买大麻的那几个家伙都是混蛋
And the guys he got it from were a couple of shitheads.
其中有个叫迪兹的疯子 还有他的朋友 叫啥来的？
A nutjob named deeds and his junkie buddy-- what was his name?
蒂姆·布伦南 原供词里就有他
Tim Brennan. He was in the original statement.
就是这个家伙
That's the guy.
他和他们俩一起出去 还是一个？
He was going to see them both? Or only one?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
但鲍勃和马文呢？
But Bob saginowski and cousin Marv?
- 你想让他当替罪羊？ - 不，我只是...
-You trying to tie them to this? -Nah, I just--
你把我单独带到这儿
you got me out here in front of the guys
和我一起的人还以为我是告密者
I work with, looking like a snitch.
真是太谢谢你了，但马文呆的地方？
Thanks for that. But cousin Marv's place?
那是我的酒吧，别和我的酒吧过去不，好么
That's my bar. All right? Don't fuck with my bar.
你知道，我...
You know, I'm...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不介意，你认识他
I don't care if you know him.
这只是...
It's just that...
他打招呼的方式，好像有些特殊的含义
...the way that he said hi, you know, it sounded like it meant something.
我就是问问
I was just asking.
他还说了什么？
What else did he say?
他说，洛克是他的
He said that rocco was his.
他还说狗身上有芯片，还证明给我看
That he has a chip in his neck to prove it.
他曾经是我的男朋友
He used to be my boyfriend.
一开始，他很迷人
In the beginning, he was charming.
他是个好人
He was really nice.
我知道有很多人说他的坏话，但我从不深究
I know a lot of people said things about him, but I don't judge people.
我不会听别人乱说
I don't want to prejudge people.
当然
Sure.
后来发生太多事
It just became too much.
我已经有一阵没看到他了，我以为他走了
I haven't seen him in a while. I thought he was gone.
对不起
I'm sorry.
很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
- 对不起  - 你不必解释
-I'm sorry. -You don't have to explain.
每个人都有过去
Everybody has a past.
如果这个家伙把洛克放到你的垃圾桶
And if this guy put rocco in your trash
那不是你的错
that's not your fault.
就算是洛克 它也不会责怪你 对吗
And as for rocco, he won't blame you.
You know?
他再清楚不过了
He don't know no better.
他比你想象的难缠
He's not just going to go away.
Eric? 不
Eric? No.
他其实并没有我想象的那么意外
He doesn't strike me as the type that wants to do that.
是的
He's not.
他杀死了一个叫里奇的孩子
He killed a kid named glory days.
是啊，听说了
Yeah. I heard that.
已经听说了
I heard that.
里奇 惠兰
Richie whelan.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
他不喜欢我问“为什么”
He's not a big fan of "why". Eric.
坏了
It's broken.
是的，没错
Yeah, it is.
你能帮我修好么
Do you want me to fix it?
- 你要修好他？ - 是啊
-You want to fix it? -Yeah.
当然
Sure.
你要来一杯么
You want another beer?
好的
Yeah.
我听说马文不是那个酒吧的主人
So I heard that cousin Marv doesn't own the bar?
冷酷的人都是这样
That some hard guys do.
但你不是那么冷酷无情
But you're not a hard guy.
那么，你为什么在这里工作
So why do you work there?
你知道我跟马文很有交情，对吧？
You know me and cousin Marv go way back, right?
是啊，马文实际上是我的堂兄
Yeah, Marv is actually my cousin.
真的？
Yeah?
马文 还有他的妹妹，多蒂...
Marv and his sister, dottie...
......他的父亲和我的母亲，他们都是姐妹
...his father and my mother, they're all sisters.
真的吗？
Really?
难道他们共用化妆品
Did they share makeup?
为什么要这样做
Why would they do that?
你说他们是“姐妹”
You said they were sisters.
你说得对，我都忘了，你知道我的意思
You're right. Yeah. You know what I mean.
为啥你取笑我这个
Why are you jumping on me like that?
- 这很有趣 - 有趣儿
-It's fun. -Fun.
有趣
Fun.
是啊，马文还以为他是一个坚强的家伙
Yeah, Marv thought he was a tough guy.
我们之前有一帮人
We had a crew once.
早些年，当我们年轻的时候，我们赚了一些钱...
Back in the day, when we was young, we made a little money...
...但好景不长，你知道...
...but it was never, you know...
所以所有人卷铺盖进城...
So a mean crew rolls into town,
and, you know...
......我们有人退缩了，就解散了
...we flinched. That's it. End of the crew.
但你还是在那种生活中
But you're still in the life.
我？不
Me? No.
不，不，不行
No. No, no, no.
我只是在照看酒吧而已
I just tend the bar.
你在干什么？进来
What are you doing? Get in.
你他妈的居然来这里了
You fucking come out here.
你疯了吗？外边冷死了，快上车
Are you nuts? It's freezing! Get in.
我不上车
I'm not getting in the car!
你以为后备箱有塑胶炸弹吗？
You think the trunk's lined with plastic?
我怎么会知道？
How should I know?
那你自己去看看
Here, go look then. Go ahead.
别跟我耍花样，想都别想
Don't you fuck with me. Don't you fucking dare!
-没人耍你  -明白吗？
-Nobody's fucking with you. -You hear?
- 好吧  - 是啊
-All right? -Yeah.
想打电话给你妈妈，告诉她你还没事？
Want to call your mommy and tell her you're okay?
别开玩笑，上次次有人看到我的弟弟还活着的时候
Don't joke. Last time anybody saw my brother alive
就是他上了别人的车
he got in a car with a guy.
好吧
All right.
你说得对，抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
冷静
Take it easy.
我们现在做的是高风险高回报的事
What we got here is a risk-versus-reward kind of thing.
我们准备好冒险
We took the risk. And up to now
到现在为止事情还算顺利
it's not been working out so well, I know.
是啊，但是呢
Yeah, but?
但我知道下次超级碗时“包裹”会出现在哪里
But I know where the super bowl drop off will be.
所以，如果你想为布莱恩报仇
So if you want to hit them back for br
没有比这更好的机会
you hit them back for a million.
这是自杀，他妈的自杀
It's suicide. Fucking suicide.
我有个消息要告诉你
I got news for you, fitzy.
我们早就死了，只不过像活死人一样
We're dead already, we're just walking around.
唯一出路 就是离开。
The only way to get out is to leave.
我不会再打劫了
I'm not doing another one, man.
- 你不干了？ - 我不干了
-You're not?
-I'm not.
- 你确定吗？ - 恩，我确定
-You sure about that? -Yeah, I'm sure.
好吧，那事后我们两清
Okay, I'll square it with you then.
我会找人来一起做的
I'm buying something with it.
首先，你不要跟任何人说我们谈论的事
First, you don't tell anybody what we just discussed.
谁都不能说
You don't tell anybody.
第二，我需要个地方躲几天
Second, I need a place to hole up for a couple days.
什么，没地方住？
What, you're on the street?
- 后备箱没关 - 我关了的
-You didn't close the trunk. -I closed it.
没关系了
Not very well.
我关上了的啊
I closed that fucking thing.
别管后备箱了，我也没睡大街上
Forget about the trunk. No, I'm not on the street.
所有人都知道我住的地方
Everybody knows where I live.
但没有人知道你住在哪里
Nobody knows where you live.
所以，今晚或明晚 可以和你住一起吗？
So can I shack up with you tonight or maybe tomorrow night?
不 不行 但我知道一个地方可以
Not with me, but I know a place.
明白了吗?
All right?
有电线吗？
Got cable?
- 什么东西？ - 线
-Motherfucker, what? -You know, cable.
去你的
Fuck you.
你必须去后边，两只手用点力
You have to get behind it! Slam it with two hands!
就是这儿
Here you are.
晚安
Good night.
我来吧
I got that.
鲍勃？
Bob?
谢谢
Thanks.
谢什么
For what?
晚安
Good night.
对不起，让你等了那么久
Sorry I was so long.
没把你带上，想吃东西吗
I didn't take you with me. You want a Chewie?
给
Here.
给你的
There you go. For you.
- 介意我坐下吗？ - 不，坐吧
-Mind if I sit down? -No, have a seat.
什么事？
What's up?
我在想，为什么你不喜欢我的堂兄
I was wondering
why you don't like my cousin.
他带走我的狗
He took my dog.
他没有
He didn't take your dog.
是你虐待那条狗，并丢在垃圾桶的
You beat the crap out of it and put it in a trash can.
我感觉那么做很不对
I felt bad about it.
这样行吗
That count?
行
Yeah.
好吧
Okay, good.
然后现在你想要回来了
And now you want it back.
我不知道该怎么说？我不知道我想要什么
What kind of question is that? I don't know what I want.
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我不想看着他带着那条狗到处玩
But I don't want him walking around thinking he's the shit.
他得明白
He needs to learn.
明白什么？
Learn what?
明白他不应该跟我作对
That he shouldn't have fucked with me.
你也想插一脚？
Are you fucking with me?
我？不，不
Me? No, no.
我已经太老啦，我更喜欢和平解决
I'm too old for that shit. I come in peace.
为啥这么说，有战争吗
Why is that? Is there a war?
据我所知并非如此
Not that I know of.
很好
Good.
在酒吧有天晚上 你让我堂兄很紧张
In the bar the other night, you made my cousin nervous.
那是很少见
You don't see that often.
我想 我们俩之间有种办法可以解决...
I think there's a way you and I can sort that out...
...让大家都开心的方法
...and both be happy.
看看你，你看起来不错
Look at you. You're looking good.
Eric deeds的精神分析档案
Eric deeds' psych file.
给你三分钟时间读，最好别弄脏那些档案
You got three minutes to read it.There better be no grease on those fingers.
哦，真该死
Well, I'll be damned.
说的好像你很惊讶一样
Like you fucking weren't already?
什么？不是你想象的那样吗？
What? Not what you were expecting?
我的文件？
My file?
是啊
Yeah.
你知道你该做什么了吧
You know what you're gonna do?
你给我1万
You got to give me 10.
1万元 明天早上
Ten grand. By tomorrow morning.
- 我哪有1万美元 - 拜托
-Who's got $10,000? -Come on.
听着，如果你想要狗 给我1万.就是这样
Listen. You want the dog, you give me 10. Simple.
听着，伙计 你不能这样闯入别人的生活
Listen here, pal. You can't walk into people's lives
然后期望别人...
and expect them to--
听我说，别激动
listen, listen. Take it easy. Listen to me.
这就是生活 生活就是这样
That is life. That's what it is.
像我这样的人 当你不注意的时候就找上门了
People like me coming along when you're not looking.
把钱给我 10点 在你家 好吗？
Just get my money, 10:00 A.M., your place, okay?
如果没有钱，那我就打电话给警察，要回我的狗
And if you don't get it, I'll go to the cops and get my dog back.
很简单，然后我会假装忘记给他吃的
Simple. And then I'll forget to feed it for a while.
之后你就会听到狗 奄奄一息...
And then when the dog gets all yappy about it...
...我会用石头打烂它的头
...I'll beat his fucking head with a rock.
好吗 你想象下
All right? You picture that.
就这样
Yeah.
还记得我对里奇惠兰做的事儿吗
Remember what I did to Richie whelan.
恩
Yep.
我想说 我有个同伙 现在他也还在帮我
And I had a partner back then. I still have him.
你没问题吧
You okay?
很好 很高兴见到你
Okay. It was good to see you.
- 鲍勃 还好吗 - 还行 你呢？
-Bobby, how's it going? -Good. You?
也不赖
Good.
怎了了 我以为你提前退休了
What's happening? I thought you took early retirement.
还能干什么 我还要继续干一两年吧
What can you do? I'll do another year or two.
希望我的静脉炎不要更严重 明白我的感受了吗 马文
Hope the phlebitis don't get too bad. See how I feel. Marv?
我要去上班了
I'm heading out to work.
-多蒂 工作愉快  - 你也是！
-Good day, dot. -You, too!
你要吃点什么吗
Are you going to eat something?
恩
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
明天是个大日子 你电话却打不通
Biggest day in the world tomorrow, I can't get you on the phone.
是的 我忘了告诉你 我感觉不太好
Yeah. I forgot to tell you, I don't feel good...
...所以我不去了
...so I'm not coming in.
叫别人去吧
Call the bartemps.
我已经叫了
I did already.
超级碗决赛 我们会需要人手的
Super bowl. We always use them.
-那你需要我干什么？ -不需要
-So what do you need me for? -I don't.
但是...
But...
...一年中最赚钱的日子 你居然不来
...you're blowing off the biggest tip day of the year.
是麽 我现在是为小费打工的人吗？
What, I work for tips now?
你有没有走过正门...
You ever go to the front of the bar...
...看看酒吧上的名字 是谁的名字
...and look at the sign on the bar? Whose name is on it?
是我的名字
That's my name.
因为曾经 酒吧是我的
'Cause I used to own it once.
是啊 你一直在说这个事
Yeah, you been playing that flute a long time now.
你处理事情总是很莽撞...
And you've been awfully fresh since...
...跟那家伙 惹上狗的事儿
...you got that dog that you mistake for a kid.
马文 木已成舟
Marv, you can't redo it.
哦？他们逼迫 你就逃避
All right? They pressed, you blinked.
已经结束了
It's done. It's over.
已经结束有一阵子了
It's been over for a while now.
好吧 我不是那种浪费一生去等待开始的人
Well, I'm not the guy who wasted his entire life waiting for it to start.
我是那种人吗？
I did that?
至少我有过一次
At least I had something once.
我曾备受尊敬 也曾恐惧过
I was respected. I was feared.
当我走进一个地方
When I walked into a place
所有人都会挺直腰板面对我 我就是焦点
people sat up. They sat up straight. They noticed.
你曾经有过什么？
What'd you ever have?
你给那老女人座位
And the fucking bar stool you put that old biddy at.
不要以为我不知道你请他喝酒是干什么
You don't think I don't know that you did it on purpose?
那本来是我的位子
That was my stool and nobody sat on that stool
因为那是马文的座位
because it was cousin Marv's
那就是有意义的
And that meant something.
是有代表性的
That meant something!
但并不是
But it didn't.
从来没有
Ever.
那只是个座位
It was just a stool.
你要做什么绝望的事情吗？
Are you doing something desperate?
又一次？
Again?
马文？
Marv?
你是要做什么
Are you doing something
我们这次也无法收拾的事情吗？
that maybe we can't clean up this time?
我告诉过你 我只是不舒服
I told you, I don't feel good.
要不你滚出去吧
So why don't you get the fuck out of here?
真的
Really.
再见，马文
Good-bye, Marv.
我希望你快点恢复
I hope you feel better soon.
别要忘了吃东西
Don't forget to eat something.
愿主保佑
The body of Christ.
可以走了吗？
Should we go?
我们走吧
Let's move out.
洛克，我得把你锁在这里一会
Rocco, I'll have to lock you down in a sec.
今天日子难熬
We have a long day.
嘿，迪迪，你还好吗？
Hey, didi, how you doing?
我得...我得和你谈谈
I got to...I got to talk to you.
我今晚想带你去个地方
I want to take you someplace tonight.
会很有意思的
It's a lot of fun.
之后我们就离开这里
Then we're out of here.
嘿  你还好吗
Hi. How you doing?
你想干什么？
What do you want?
我不希望你在这里 你走吧
I don't want you here. Please leave.
不 听我说 坐下来 听我说 好吗
No, listen to me. Sit down and listen to me, okay?
我希望你离开 这是我的家
I want you to go. This is my home.
我已经不是你女朋友了 请离开
I'm not your girl anymore. I want you to leave.
拜托 坐下嘛
Come on, take a seat. Come on.
别跟我玩这一套了 坐下
Don't play that shit. Sit down.
你看起来还不错 顺便说说
You look good, by the way.
今晚我们要去个地方 会很有意思的
We're going somewhere tonight. It's gonna be a lot of fun.
之后 我们就离开这里
And after that, we're out of here.
我只想你离开 拜托
I want you to go. Please.
你会一起来
You're going to go.
而且打扮的漂漂亮亮的 好吗
And make yourself pretty, all right?
很高兴见到你，伙计
Good to see you, man.
- 你去哪儿了？ - 我回来看你，吉米
-Where you been? -I came back to see you, Jimmy.
他说，我马上回来给你
He said, I'm coming right back for you.
女士们 先生们 请起立 摘掉帽子
Ladies and gentlemen,
please rise and remove your hats...
...用歌声来歌颂我们的祖国
...as we honor America with the singing of our national anthem.
两杯啤酒 三杯阿莫斯特 两杯杰克丹尼 一瓶岩石
Two dos equis, three amstel, two shots of Jack and a Dewar's on the rocks.
- 你听到了吗 rardy？ - 来了
-You hear that, rardy? -Coming up.
嘿，鲍勃？
Hey, Bob?
鲍勃？
Bob?
鲍勃！
Bob!
能给1-3台加两瓶喜力啤酒吗？
Can I get two more Heineken on 1-3?
Rardy？两瓶喜力啤酒
Rardy? Two more Heineken.
- 白酒 对吧？ - 恩
-White wine, right?
-Yeah.
能给我一杯斯特利 然后给这位女士一份沙拉吗？
Can you get me a stoli rocks and a house chard for the lady?
我今天早上没看到你
I didn't see you this morning.
是啊 怎么了
Yeah, so what?
所以，你不想要钱了？
So you don't want the money?
- 你带了吗？ - 什么？
-You bring it? -What?
钱你带来了吗
Did you bring the money?
你给我的印象就是会带钱来的那种人
You strike me as the type who would bring it.
- 两杯斯特拉一杯阿姆斯特尔 - 好的
-Two Stella and an amstel.  -Sure.
Rardy 两杯斯特拉 一杯阿姆斯特尔
Rardy, two amstels and a Stella.
她为什么在这里
Why is she here?
她是我女朋友
She's my girl.
把那纸给我 你就可以拿走钱了
Give me that piece of paper and you get the money.
什么纸？
What paper?
宠物注册证件 还有芯片 说好的
The microchip and the license, like we agreed.
为什么呢
Why would I do that?
因为这就是我付钱给你的原因 说好的
Because that's why I'm paying you the money. That's the deal.
好像是这么说的 等一下
That's a deal. Hold on a second.
你可以把零钱留着
You can keep the change. Keep the change.
两杯斯特拉 一杯阿姆斯特尔
Two stellas and one amstel.
怎么了 等一下
What's up? Wait a minute.
我现在不方便说话 等下
I can't talk right now. Wait a second.
现在说吧
Here you go.
怎么这么吵 你在哪儿
What's that noise? Where are you?
我在那儿呢 你的地方
I'm at the place. Your place.
酒吧？
The bar?
你为什么去这么早？
Why the fuck you show up so early?
本来很简单的 你按时出现 做完该做的 然后走人
This was simple. You show up at the designated time, do the thing and leave.
我知道他看起来像什么 但是我跟你说你别玩他
I know what he seems like, but I shit you not, do not fuck with him.
离他远点 他已经觉得你要为了这条狗杀了他
Stay away from him. He already thinks you want to kill him over some fucking dog.
别管那么多
Just stay in the back.
好的 我明白
Yeah, I got it.
现在在酒吧 别喝多了
And you're in a bar. Don't drink too much.
两点还要碰头 你个白痴
I'll see you at 2:00, you fucking idiot.
多有意思的比赛
What an amazing game!
27-23 最终得分
Twenty-seven to 23, your final score!
- 你跟他在一起吗？ - 不
-Are you with him? -No.
那你为什么来这里？
So why are you here?
- 你们聊什么呢？ - 我告诉你 没什么
-What were you talking about? -I told you, nothing.
鲍勃
Bob.
是啊 我们聊过了
Yeah, we do.
这好像有问题 情况不妙
This is not good. This is so not good.
我不想来这里
I don't want to be here.
我没想过来这里
I didn't want to come here.
我还没回去 他就在我家等我了
He was waiting in my house when I got home.
对不起，鲍勃
I'm sorry, Bob.
他带着枪
He has a gun.
我要去洗手间了
I'm going to the ladies'.
你们说什么呢？
What were you talking about?
橄榄球
Football.
再给我一杯 好吗
Give me another shot, will you?
你搭档叫什么？
What was the name of your partner?
你知道他也不会对他有什么威胁吧，鲍勃？
Wouldn't be much of a threat if you knew who he was, would he, Bob?
不会的，但是...
Yeah, but...
...他帮你杀里奇惠兰，对不对？
...he helped you kill Richie whelan, right?
鲍勃 那是个传闻
That's the rumor, Bob.
不只是传闻 你自己说的
More than a rumor. It's what you said.
那就当它是真的 鲍勃 几点了
Then it's more than a rumor, Bob. What time is it?
你不用一直叫我鲍勃
You know, you don't have to keep calling me Bob all the time.
我会尽量不叫的 鲍勃 那是什么
I'll see what I can do, Bob. What is that?
你想要的1万块
The 10 grand you wanted.
这是1万块？
This is 10 grand?
是的
Yeah.
你知道我怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
我两点要看下保险柜里的
I'm going to look in the safe at 2:00.
时间锁两点整会失效 你有90秒的时间关闭它..
Time lock goes off at 2:00 A.M. you got 90 seconds to close it...
...或者触发两个无声报警
...or it triggers two silent alarms.
我们两点得看下保险箱
We should look in the safe at 2:00.
你听着
Now you listen.
那只狗 我很乐意花1万块买下
I'm happy to pay you 10 grand for the dog.
是啊 一万买一条狗
Yeah. Ten grand for the dog.
但仅此而已
But that's it.
那她多少钱呢？
And how much for her?
这个呢 她值多少钱
How about that?
How much should he pay for you?
Eric 求你了 别这样
Eric, please. Please don't do this.
- 马文呢 - 马文？
-Where's Marv? -Marv?
你找他干什么
You need him for something?
我不想干什么
I don't want anything.
我只是不想让他突然出现在我身后
I just don't want him creeping up my back all of a sudden.
是啊，我亲爱的堂兄马文
Yeah, my sweet cousin Marv.
你知道他也有一些麻烦
You know he's had some trouble, Marv. Yeah.
比如 10年前 他...
Like, about 10 years ago, man, he had...
...那些牌有问题
...a problem with the cards.
这我还不知道 鲍勃
I didn't know that, Bob.
但这之后他更像 放高利贷的人
But he was more of a loan shark back then.
我记得这小子...
And I remember this kid...
...他很喜欢他的钱
...he was into him for a shitload of money.
对狗和篮球可以说无可救药
Hopeless case when it came to the dogs and b-ball.
后来走上不归路
Just degenerate, really
就是那种怎么都还不上钱的孩子
Kind of kid who'd never be able to pay back what he owed.
现在1:57了 好吗
It's 1:57, all right?
然后那孩子去了药店 他...
And then the kid goes to a.C. And he...
...在收银机里抢了2万2钱美元
...hits up a slot machine for 22 grand.
骗你的
Bam.
是谁的主意？
Who'd have thunk it?
这就是因为他欠了马文的钱
It was, like, a fraction more than what he owed Marv.
是因为他还不了钱 然后你们逼迫他的
So he didn't pay up and you roughed him up.
不 不是这样 他把钱还给了马文 分文不差
No, no. That's not what happened. He paid back Marv, every cent.
他是一个好人
He was a good guy.
已经1:58 好吗
It's 1:58, all right?
他没想到的是马文找到了他藏东西的地方
What he didn't account for was Marv skimming off his own stash.
因为他的习惯还有他的赌债
Because of his habits and his gambling debts.
这孩子意外的...带着2万2千块钱的...
And this kid coming out of the blue with 22 grand was a...
...他怎么说来的？
...what'd he say?
“一个可行的商业机会。”
"A viable business opportunity."
这就是我的堂兄马文
That's my cousin Marv.
只要没人知道 他把钱还给马文了
So long as nobody knew that he'd paid Marv back off, you know?
你明白会发生什么吗？
You see where this is going?
知道 那孩子必须被榨干
Yeah, kid had to be ripped off.
不 那孩子不得不被杀掉
No. Kid had to be killed.
所以这样就没人知道他把钱给马文了
So nobody'd know he'd paid Marv back off.
所以我们也是一样
So that's what we did.
所以 你...
So you...
-  ...杀了他。 - 是的 我杀了他
-...killed him. -Yeah, I did.
我照着他的脸开了两枪
I shot him in the face, twice.
然后用毛巾捂住他的头 照着心脏捅了两刀
Then I wrapped his head in a towel and stabbed him in the heart...
...他这样就会流血 我就把他放到浴缸 然后看他流血身亡
...so he would bleed out, put him in my bathtub and watched him drain.
死后我把它放进 油罐里...
Then I put him in an oil tank...
...倒上洗衣粉还有碱液...
...with laundry detergent and lye...
...然后封起来
...and sealed it back up.
想知道他的名字吗？
Want to know what his name was?
两点了 鲍勃 已经两点了
It's 2:00, Bob. It's 2:00.
他的名字
His name.
- 我不知道的 鲍勃 - 你知道 这是你知道的事儿
-I would not know, Bob.  -Yes, you do. This is something you know.
- 我怎么会知道 鲍勃 - 猜猜看
-I wouldn't know that, Bob. -Guess.
现在已经两点了 而你得打开保险柜
I know it's 2:00,
and you got to open the safe!
听我说
Listen to me.
他的名字...
His name...
...叫做 里奇惠兰
...was Richie whelan.
大家都叫他光辉岁月？
Everybody called him glory days?
我杀了里奇惠兰，好吗？
I killed Richie whelan, okay?
当然了
Sure you did.
该死的小混混
Fucking punk.
出去吃晚宴 你却穿的像睡衣 还穿着..
Go out to dinner dressed like you're still in your living room. You wear those...
...小丑一样的鞋子
...big hippity-hoppity clown shoes.
对女人说话凶狠 对她们很卑鄙
You speak to women terribly. You treat them despicably.
还伤害无辜的狗 我已经受不了你了 混蛋
You hurt harmless dogs that can't defend themselves. I'm tired of you, man.
我受够你了 你真让我难堪
I'm tired of you. You embarrass me.
你知道 他会一直回来
You know, he would have kept coming back.
像这样的人 你让他们得逞
People like this, you let them take something from you...
...他们就会一直找你
...and they keep coming back.
你就会欠他们一辈子
You still owe them and they never, never change.
你永远改变不了这种人的想法
You can never change their mind.
你刚才...
You just...
我是说 你刚杀了他
I mean, you just fucking shot him.
是的 我杀了他 没错 他本来打算伤害我们的狗的
Yes, I did. Absolutely.
He was going to hurt our dog.
鲍勃？
Bob?
我...我可以走了吗？
Can I...Can I go now?
是的，你可以走了
Yeah, of course. You can.
所以 你就这样让我走了？
So you...You'll let me go?
当然了
Sure, sure.
为什么不？
Why not?
以后没人会伤害你了 好吗
And, and nobody will ever hurt you again. Okay?
都结束了 好吗
This is done. Okay?
东西都拿了吗
You got your stuff?
走吧
Go on now.
但是现在...你以为我会说出去吗
But now...Now you'll think I'll talk.
我不会说出去的 鲍勃
I won't talk, Bob.
我知道你不会说
I know you won't.
我保证 我不会
I promise. I won't.
纳迪亚 你不用 不用为这种人 他们不会...
Nadia, you can't. Not with these people. They won't--
是你这类人 鲍勃
your people, Bob.
不 他们跟我...我和他们不一样
No, they're not my-- I'm not them.
我也不是这样的
And I'm not this.
你看起来过得不错
You've seen better days, huh?
安德烈？
Andre?
他刚进来
He just came in.
是啊 没错 我打开门的时候
Yeah, that's right. When I opened up the door.
我刚让米莉离开...
I was just letting Millie out, and...
用枪指着你的脸 ，但你说“今晚不行”是吗
Put a gun in your face, but you said, "not tonight," huh?
我什么也没说
I didn't say anything.
你之前见过他吗
You ever see him before?
是的
Yeah.
是的 他在这里
Yeah, he was in here.
那边 看比赛
Over there, watching the game.
因为他是一个人 所以我留意了
Caught my attention' cause he was on his own.
也许他不是呢
Maybe he wasn't.
- 不 他是的  - 或者也许不是
-No, he was, though. -Or maybe he wasn't.
对不起，我没听明白
I'm sorry, I don't follow you.
你当然明白 你说他是自己一个人
Sure you do. You say he was on his own, alone.
我说他不是 有什么听不懂
I say he wasn't. What's to follow?
你
You.
你是一个人
You're alone.
有时一个人挺好的
Sometimes it's good to be alone.
说吧
Say it.
我是一个人
I'm alone.
不可能 伙计 你有朋友
No way, my man. You have friends.
说到朋友，你的堂兄马文呢
Speaking of friends, your cousin Marv?
他跟我说他退休了 想让你接管这个酒吧
He told me he's retiring. He want you to be the boss of the bar.
我说“当然可以 这是你的酒吧。”
I said, "of course, it's your bar."
“但钱不是你的”
"But it's not your money."
“所以你为什么老想着拿走我的钱？”
"So why you always trying to take my money?"
于是我给他一个约定
So I made him a deal.
“你和你吸毒的朋友 别碰我的钱...
"You and your druggy friends leave my money alone...
...我会付钱给你 足够让你去个安静的地方”
...and I'll pay you a ticket to a nice, quiet place."
你觉得呢？
So what do you think?
给酒吧换个名字 挂上“鲍勃的酒吧”。
Take down his name, put up yours. "Bob's bar."
听起来怎么样“鲍勃的酒吧”。
Has a nice ring to it, huh? "Bob's bar."
“鲍勃的大酒吧”
"Bob's big bad bar."
我开玩笑的 朋友 别生气
I'm kidding, my friend. Lighten up.
当然
Sure.
- 他合适吗？ - 恩 不得不打断他的腿 但挺合适的
-Did he fit? -Yeah. Had to break his legs, but he fit fine.
笑一个 别介意 一切都会好起来的
Smile. Don't mind, everything's gonna be okay.
好好休息下吧
Get some rest.
晚安
Good night.
有一些罪恶承认了 就无法挽回...
There are some sins you commit that you can't come back from...
...无论你多么努力
...no matter how hard you try.
就是无法挽回 就好像恶魔 等着占据你的身体
You just can't, you know? It's like the devil is waiting for your body to quit.
因为他知道...他知道...
Because he knows...He knows that...
...他已经得到了你的灵魂
...he already owns your soul.
然后我想 也许根本没有恶魔
And then I think, maybe, you know, there is no devil.
你死了 上帝会说：
You die, and God, he says:
“不”
"Nah."
“不，你不能进天堂”
"Nah, you can't come in."
“你必须离开”
"You have to leave now."
“你必须离开，你必须孤独一个人”
"You have to leave and go away and you have to be alone."
“你必须孤独终老”
"You have to be alone forever."
关于马文的事 我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about cousin Marv.
他们说是汽车抢劫案件
It was a carjacking gone bad is what they said.
劫车？ 没错
Carjacking? Right.
那还真是不幸
That was an execution.
那儿里这个酒吧 只有一条街的距离
A block and a half from this bar.
不管怎样 我真的很抱歉
Anyway, it fucking sucks and I'm really sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
明天教堂关闭仪式 你去么
Are you going to the church closing tomorrow?
当然
Yeah, of course.
我还不知道 我得加班
I don't know yet. I got a shift.
他们把教堂卖了 卖给Milligan地产 我跟你说过吗？
They sold it. To milligan development. What'd I tell you?
会变成带彩色玻璃的公寓
Condos with stained glass windows.
Eric deeds.
我跟你提到过一次
I mentioned him to you once.
恩 我记得
Yeah, I remember.
- 你没回答 - 我记得你提过他
-You didn't then. -I remember you mentioning him.
他周日就在这个酒吧里 你见到他了吗？
He was in this bar super bowl Sunday. You see him?
没有 因为周日超级碗决赛酒吧有好多人 所以...
No. There was a lot of people in here on super bowl Sunday, so...
是啊 没错
Yeah, that's true.
只是 这里是他最后来过的地方...
It's just this was the last place he was ever seen and then...
就像里奇惠兰一样
Just like Richie whelan.
太讽刺了 因为传说Eric deeds是杀害惠兰的凶手
Ironic, 'cause deeds supposedly killed whelan.
尸体都找不到了...
Bodies getting clipped or vanishing all over the place, but...
...拜托 老兄 你真的没看到什么？
...come on, man, you don't see anything?
没有 这儿就这么大地方 对吧
Nah. You know, that's this neighborhood, right?
但他也许还会出现的
But he could turn up.
有些人就是这样
People do all the time.
没错 如果他出现 也可能在精神病院
That's true. If he does, it'll probably be in a psych ward.
惠兰失踪的那晚 他就在精神病院
Which is where he was the night whelan disappeared.
我没说谎 是真的
I'm not lying. It's true.
Eric deeds总是在当替罪羊
Deeds always took credit for the whelan hit‘
因为没人想背惠兰的黑锅
'cause nobody else wanted to.
他觉得 这样可以帮他维护他的街头信誉...
He thought it would help his street cred...
...但他没有杀惠兰
...but he didn't kill whelan.
他没有？
He didn't?
是的
Yeah.
没人看到你 对吧 鲍勃？
No one ever sees you coming, do they, Bob?
洛克 我们有事要做
Rocco. Something we got to do.
当你离开酒吧的时候 我就知道那是永别
When you left the bar, I know that meant stay away.
我知道 再也不见 但是你没说出口
I know that meant stay away, but you didn't say it.
所以 如果你说出来 那...
So if you say it, then...
...我就会离开 相信我纳迪亚 我现在就走
...I will just go. Believe me, Nadia, I will leave right now.
但你得亲口说出来
But you have to say it.
我去拿下外套
Let me go get my jacket.
啊
Yeah?
太好了 当然
Sure，great Great.
---==FRDS作品 感谢观赏==--